I see.
So you're an adventurer.
I wanted to be one a long time ago.
It was the kind of dumb
childhood dream everyone has.
Like a fairy tale
It's a sign the story has reached its end
Like a single passage taken from
A journey that was too long
Of the evil that once cast a shadow
Across this land
And the memories of the short journey
With the hero who defeated it
The story ends
And the hero goes to sleep
Leaving this land with
Days of peace and quiet
The passage of time heartlessly
Makes people forget
Even the tracks left behind by his life
Begin to rust
Just the same
Your words and wishes and courage
Are still inside of me
And they live on
We chose the same path
That's all it was supposed to be
Why is it that at some point
I wanted to understand the reason for
The tears that fall down my cheeks
Even now
If I retrace the journey we walked together
Even though you're not there
I know I'll be able to find it
When I was a kid,
I had a friend who I joined
on lots of little adventures.
Foolhardy and with energy to spare,
he was like a gorilla.
That said, he was a good gorilla
who cared for his friends.
When I grew up and started
to forget that dream,
he invited me to become
an adventurer with him.
I wonder what would've changed
if I'd taken his hand then.
That was ten years ago.
I still regret it.
Huh.
So why are you telling me this?
My village's harvest festival is coming up.
My brother asked me to go into the woods
and pick wild herbs to use in cooking.
But then...
I got stuck in a bottomless swamp.
I'm done for.
But if you take my hand,
then maybe my fate will change.
Hold on. I'm thinking about it.
What is there to think about?
Your hand is dirty.
This is really not the time
to be worrying about that!
Besides, miss...
Grown-ups are dirty by nature.
This might be my first time encountering
a physically dirty adult.
Can I have some more time?
I'm trying to remember the spell to pull
someone out of a bottomless swamp.
P-Please hurry.
Let's see...
Ms. Frieren.
Did you find any herbs?
Oh, I remember now.
This is far enough.
I'm sorry for the trouble
Ms. Frieren caused you.
It's fine. She saved me.
I'll give her an earful later.
Not my problem.
Anyway, are you sure you don't
need to stop by the village?
We're busy preparing for the harvest festival,
but I can at least thank you.
We're hoping to reach a large
town today so we can resupply.
I see. In that case, be careful.
There are lots of dangerous
venomous creatures around here.
Okay.
Got it.
Something bit me.
What? You were bitten?
He told us to be careful.
What are you doing?
Let's stop the bleeding.
Huh?
My nose is starting to bleed.
Identifying poison is a priest spell,
so I'm not too good at it.
I don't recognize this reaction,
so the antidotes we have might not work.
We should get you checked out at a church.
Fern, how much longer can
you use your flying magic?
It consumes a lot of mana,
so only about thirty minutes.
Thirty minutes won't get us to town.
We'll head back to that village.
I'll transport Stark.
It's not that big a deal.
I'm fine.
Besides, my master said
you can tough out poisons.
Come to think of it, Eisen was perfectly
healthy even after taking several arrows
that were coated with a poison
strong enough to knock out a dragon.
Heiter was appalled.
See?
That just goes to show that Mr. Eisen
was far from normal.
Besides, according to Mr. Heiter,
20% of adventurer deaths are due to poison.
We should hurry.
I'm fine, really.
It's too late.
In a few hours, his brain
will begin to melt.
It will flow out his nose,
and then he'll die.
That's terrifying!
Isn't there anything we can do, Father?
Normally, it can only be
cured if it's treated early,
but perhaps my brother could help.
Brother, do you have a minute?
Don't you think this new
tub is kind of small?
There's honor in poverty.
Isn't this going too far, though?
We're the only ones who impoverish
ourselves down to a hand-sized tub.
More importantly, Sein,
take a look at this boy.
Huh? Brother, these are the
ones I told you about.
They're the people who rescued me.
Did you get bitten by a snake?
I told you to be careful.
Now we're even.
Brother, I'm going to help out at the plaza.
Sure.
My nose stopped bleeding.
The effects of the poison are gone.
Father, is he...?
What do you think of my younger brother?
That holy symbol around your neck
is awarded to the most outstanding priest
in a region by the holy capital.
He instantly cured a poison a
healing expert called incurable.
He's a genius.
I'm not surprised you noticed, Ms. Frieren.
You know who I am?
Mr. Heiter told me about you.
He gave me this holy symbol when he came
here from the holy capital to observe us.
That said, I'm a mere provincial priest.
This is the only thing I can be proud of.
But my ability doesn't compare to Sein's.
Our parents passed away when we were young.
Since then, I raised my much
younger brother myself.
As a child, he often said he wanted
to become an adventurer.
He didn't want to become
an ordinary village priest like me
who spent every day the same way.
He said that with his eyes
full of hopes and dreams.
But now he's like I was when I was young.
This life must bore him.
Would you please take him
away from this village?
I'm certain he's been looking for someone
to give him that last push.
I'm in, Frieren.
What's there to even think about?
I'm not risking my brains
flowing out my nose again.
It's true that the journey ahead
may be safer with a priest.
What do you not like about
the idea, Ms. Frieren?
It's an aversion to my own kind, I guess.
What is she talking about?
I'm inviting him to join us,
even if you two don't want to.
Where is he going?
Mr. Sein spends a lot of time
at the bar downstairs.
What?
Alcohol.
Tobacco.
Gambling.
That's a bit too corrupt, don't you think?
I'm getting to know the people.
Care to join us?
It's Stark. We're looking for a priest.
Will you join us?
You must be joking.
I'm this village's priest.
I can't go on adventures.
No, I suppose that could be fun.
Have a seat, Stark.
If you can beat me, I'll join your party.
Really?
Yes, really.
Please, no!
Ms. Frieren, I think I heard
Mr. Stark scream downstairs.
Someone's taken all his belongings.
How awful. Who would do this?
No hard feelings.
What?
Grown-ups are dirty, after all.
Someone's taken all his belongings!
The village chief won the lot.
He's got the devil's own luck.
Sein.
I heard you're looking for party members.
Ask someone else.
You want to become an adventurer, don't you?
That was a long time ago. It's too late now.
I should've gone after him sooner.
The only person sitting here
is a loser in his underwear.
Frieren, come defeat the Demon King with us.
It's too late now.
I haven't fought demons in over 500 years.
I've forgotten how to fight them.
I deferred the decision for too long.
I was probably afraid to fight the Demon King.
Too much time has passed.
Time I can't get back now.
So what, Frieren?
I'm talking about the present.
Ask someone else.
You don't know how I feel.
I see. That told me everything I need to know.
I don't like you, Sein.
I see. In that case...
So I've decided you'll join us,
no matter what.
What? Why?
That makes so little sense that it scares me.
Thanks. I feel warmer now.
I'm truly sorry for all the
trouble we caused. Excuse us.
How much did it cost to get everything back?
He said we should take our time and
enjoy the harvest festival coming up,
and then he returned it all for free.
Good thing they're nice people here.
He didn't know what to do with the axe.
That's kinda sad.
Mr. Stark, please put these on.
Do you have to hold them
like they're filthy?
Mr. Sein, these are yours.
What did I do to upset her?
She's mad you took all
of Stark's belongings.
It wasn't me. It was the chief.
People who gamble are the worst.
I'm sorry, okay?
And Mr. Sein is supposed to be a priest.
I'm not so sure about a priest who drinks.
Don't you know, Ms. Frieren?
Alcohol is the best medicine.
What did you teach her, Heiter?
Whether we recruit him or not,
Sein should become an adventurer.
You've really come around to the idea.
I thought it might be nice to give
someone the push they need,
like Himmel the Hero did for me.
Looks like the adventurers
have decided to stay in town.
They've been trying
to recruit me every day since.
All my efforts to make them stop
have been in vain.
They invite me on adventures with hopes and
dreams in their eyes, like he did back then.
I'm just going to travel around
the northern lands a bit.
I'll be back in time for the harvest
festival three years from now.
If you aren't ready now, you can come then.
Let's go on our next adventure together.
Every time they try to recruit me,
I wonder, "Why now?"
They shine too brightly for these tired eyes.
You want to know what Sein likes?
We've been struggling to win him over,
so we're looking for ideas.
Well, he likes alcohol,
tobacco, and gambling...
We know those already.
Are you sure he's a priest?
It seems Mr. Heiter was a
serious priest after all.
What's a serious priest, anyway?
He also likes older women.
He's a totally depraved priest.
Older women, huh?
Honestly, I don't know what
to do with that information.
What?
Oh, right.
Brother, don't you think
our new sickle is too small?
You can't even cut grass with...
Oh, it's you again.
Do you have a minute, Sein?
You're still here?
C'mon.
Don't make me say it again.
Ask someone else.
Sein, wouldn't you like to
travel with an older woman?
Are you stupid?
That's the whole reason I wanted
to become an adventurer as a kid.
Talk about impure motives.
So, where is this older woman?
Right here, Sein.
I'm an elf. I'm far older than you are.
Come to think of it, I think
my brother mentioned that.
But an older woman like that...
is no older woman at all!
He seems really distressed.
Then you leave me with no choice.
I didn't want to do this...
but the time has come to use the seduction
technique my master taught me.
Smooch.
What was that?
I threw you a kiss.
Maybe you're too young
to appreciate it, sonny.
Won't somebody please take this child home?
That was way too sexy.
What's wrong with you two?
That's odd. When I tried it on Himmel,
it knocked him out cold.
Himmel!
You're a wicked woman.
How strange.
I understand.
If I'd been the target,
I would have been in danger.
As depraved as he is, he's still a holy man.
A formidable foe.
Enough already.
I'm not becoming an adventurer.
I thought you wanted to go after your friend.
Brother, you must understand.
Sein...
He said he'd be back in three years.
Well, it's been ten.
He's obviously dead.
So you're giving up without going to see him?
It's only been ten years.
If you don't go see him now,
you'll regret it in the near future.
You'll wonder if you could've made it
in time if you'd gone now.
It's too—
You think it's too late, don't you?
I'm talking about the present, Sein.
I can't go for the same reason
I didn't follow him ten years ago.
I can't leave my brother
behind in this village.
What are you talking about, Sein?
I overheard the conversation
you had with Mr. Heiter
when he came to observe us.
With your talent, you could serve
as a priest in the holy capital.
Me, in the holy capital?
Yes, undoubtedly.
What would happen to my brother then?
He'd come with you, of course.
I see.
Mr. Heiter, I appreciate the offer,
but my life in this village is comfortable.
My brother lost his parents
when he was still young.
As his older brother,
I can't take his hometown from him, too.
Very well.
I understand.
I suppose I wasted my time coming here.
But since I'm already wasting time,
perhaps I'll tell your brother
all about my adventures.
My brother stayed in this village for me.
Sein, is that what you thought?
We're not the same!
I've never regretted the choice I made!
But what about you?
How long do you intend
to regret your choice?
I've had enough.
I apologized to my brother.
Okay.
Don't get the wrong idea.
He's a kind brother.
He never once hit me before,
but I made him hit me this time.
I'd never seen him with
that expression before.
Frieren, I've decided to
become an adventurer.
I'm going after my friend.
It's only been ten years, after all.
I see.
I'm doing this so I can look for him.
I'll find him and make my stupid
childhood dream come true.
So I'm only traveling with you partway.
All right!
You did it.
Bye!
See you!
Bye-bye!
See you later!
Later!
By the way, where are you guys headed?
Heaven.
Is that someplace you need to seek out?
We all go there when we die.
Even you, Mr. Sein?
She really doesn't mince words, huh?
Good luck to us both.
Seriously, what's her deal?
And you alright
Can you hear me
Trailing along deserted train tracks
Crying excessively
Wanting you to smile
I hold on to memories I'd like to keep fresh
There's something I'd like to tell you
With words more precious than a goodbye
Unremarkable yet special
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
So, if I were to be born again
I would surely choose this place once more
So, if we were to meet again
I'd never let you go, I'd choose the present
Even if no promises were made
Even if I'm lost in days of loneliness
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
What do you mean by understanding relationships?
You just seem like someone accustomed
to speaking with women. I don't like it.
I'm pretty sure that would kill me.
Let's go shopping together later.
We help each other when we're in need.
It happens naturally as people age.
We're alive.
Do you really hate me that much?
Those arguments are the
privilege of the young.